[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Can it be normal for you and Jaycee?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "it", "be", "normal", "for", "you", "and", "Jaycee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jaycee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "How's she?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Pretty awesome.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "awesome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jaycee"]}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "So how easy is it to just say, OK, we're going to rebuild and get on with our lives?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "easy", "is", "it", "to", "just", "say", ",", "OK", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "rebuild", "and", "get", "on", "with", "our", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I think a lot of it depends -- is dependent upon Jaycee and her attitude.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "depends", "--", "is", "dependent", "upon", "Jaycee", "and", "her", "attitude", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Can you remember that feeling?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "remember", "that", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "I mean, like it was yesterday?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "like", "it", "was", "yesterday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "It was -- I had a really hard time accepting it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "I", "had", "a", "really", "hard", "time", "accepting", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Has your feeling subsided at all or do you feel this awful hate towards them?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "your", "feeling", "subsided", "at", "all", "or", "do", "you", "feel", "this", "awful", "hate", "towards", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I -- the hate fuels the fire for the changes that need to be made.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "the", "hate", "fuels", "the", "fire", "for", "the", "changes", "that", "need", "to", "be", "made", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jaycee"]}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "And the significance of that is what?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "significance", "of", "that", "is", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Well, it was not only the last thing that Jaycee touched that was her reality back then but it's also a symbol of new beginnings.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "not", "only", "the", "last", "thing", "that", "Jaycee", "touched", "that", "was", "her", "reality", "back", "then", "but", "it", "'s", "also", "a", "symbol", "of", "new", "beginnings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "How do you hear?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "hear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "And what was your first thought when you -- when they did that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "your", "first", "thought", "when", "you", "--", "when", "they", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "I kind of blew it off because I had heard it so many times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "kind", "of", "blew", "it", "off", "because", "I", "had", "heard", "it", "so", "many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "She knew?", "question_tokens": ["She", "knew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "She knew.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "knew", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "But she wouldn't tell you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "she", "would", "n't", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "She needed it to come from them.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "needed", "it", "to", "come", "from", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "So you called the sheriff?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "called", "the", "sheriff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "I mean, you're sensing it's good news now?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "sensing", "it", "'s", "good", "news", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I -- no, I -- no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "no", ",", "I", "--", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Do you remember?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "You were too excited?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "too", "excited", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Too excited.", "answer_tokens": ["Too", "excited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What did her voice sound like after all that time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "her", "voice", "sound", "like", "after", "all", "that", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Same, same.", "answer_tokens": ["Same", ",", "same", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Could you -- could you quite believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "--", "could", "you", "quite", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Was it like some strange fairytale ending to the nightmare?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "like", "some", "strange", "fairytale", "ending", "to", "the", "nightmare", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What emotions did you go through?", "question_tokens": ["What", "emotions", "did", "you", "go", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "All kinds.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "kinds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Can you block it out completely?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "block", "it", "out", "completely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "I have to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Understatement, right?", "question_tokens": ["Understatement", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "It is the understatement of the year.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "the", "understatement", "of", "the", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "How do you tackle that kind of emotional dilemma?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "tackle", "that", "kind", "of", "emotional", "dilemma", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, I think guilt is your word.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "guilt", "is", "your", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "How are they dealing with the reality of discovery of the whole thing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "they", "dealing", "with", "the", "reality", "of", "discovery", "of", "the", "whole", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "I think it's been extremely important that the media has respected -- thanks to the fabulous PR person, has respected their space.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "been", "extremely", "important", "that", "the", "media", "has", "respected", "--", "thanks", "to", "the", "fabulous", "PR", "person", ",", "has", "respected", "their", "space", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What's been the thing that she realized other than just seeing you again that she missed the most?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "thing", "that", "she", "realized", "other", "than", "just", "seeing", "you", "again", "that", "she", "missed", "the", "most", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Having a life.", "answer_tokens": ["Having", "a", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Does she have ambition now?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "have", "ambition", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What's been the best part of it for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "best", "part", "of", "it", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Being able to hold her.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "able", "to", "hold", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think she'll -- may meet a Mr. Right, get married, live a fairy tale life that you would imagine you wanted for your daughter?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "'ll", "--", "may", "meet", "a", "Mr.", "Right", ",", "get", "married", ",", "live", "a", "fairy", "tale", "life", "that", "you", "would", "imagine", "you", "wanted", "for", "your", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ":", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Right"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Because she's 31 now?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "she", "'s", "31", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I don't think -- she's had a normal relationship with a man at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "--", "she", "'s", "had", "a", "normal", "relationship", "with", "a", "man", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Sort of awful flashbacks, nightmares?", "question_tokens": ["Sort", "of", "awful", "flashbacks", ",", "nightmares", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "She worked through some material early on and that's where the horse work was tremendously useful with her was that some of the early difficult experiences she was able to get in touch with in the arena with the horses, with my assistant and the other therapist assistants and --", "answer_tokens": ["She", "worked", "through", "some", "material", "early", "on", "and", "that", "'s", "where", "the", "horse", "work", "was", "tremendously", "useful", "with", "her", "was", "that", "some", "of", "the", "early", "difficult", "experiences", "she", "was", "able", "to", "get", "in", "touch", "with", "in", "the", "arena", "with", "the", "horses", ",", "with", "my", "assistant", "and", "the", "other", "therapist", "assistants", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "When you bring in horses to somebody who loves animals, loves horses and so on, what's the concept for how that acts as therapy?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "bring", "in", "horses", "to", "somebody", "who", "loves", "animals", ",", "loves", "horses", "and", "so", "on", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "concept", "for", "how", "that", "acts", "as", "therapy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "AILEY: It's actually so simple that it's hard to describe sometimes.", "answer_tokens": ["AILEY", ":", "It", "'s", "actually", "so", "simple", "that", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "describe", "sometimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jaycee"]}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "How vital is that do you think to what happened?", "question_tokens": ["How", "vital", "is", "that", "do", "you", "think", "to", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "You can look at this wonderful woman right here, and you can see where so much of Jaycee's strength comes from, in her poise, in her ability to stare things straight down.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "look", "at", "this", "wonderful", "woman", "right", "here", ",", "and", "you", "can", "see", "where", "so", "much", "of", "Jaycee", "'s", "strength", "comes", "from", ",", "in", "her", "poise", ",", "in", "her", "ability", "to", "stare", "things", "straight", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "I mean, how would you sum up your feelings?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "would", "you", "sum", "up", "your", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Sadness.", "answer_tokens": ["Sadness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"], "PERSON": ["Lavelle"]}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "What did you see?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "All of 2008, I was in Vegas along with Lavelle.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "of", "2008", ",", "I", "was", "in", "Vegas", "along", "with", "Lavelle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Was he ready to go?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "ready", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "To do 50 shows?", "question_tokens": ["To", "do", "50", "shows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Did you ever see him taking drugs of any kind?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "see", "him", "taking", "drugs", "of", "any", "kind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "-- Is this another Michael stunt?", "question_tokens": ["--", "Is", "this", "another", "Michael", "stunt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "You saw that on CNN?", "question_tokens": ["You", "saw", "that", "on", "CNN", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Staples Center"]}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Where were you?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "I was at the Staples Center.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "at", "the", "Staples", "Center", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Did you see him much?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "him", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "So all this was sort of brand new to you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "all", "this", "was", "sort", "of", "brand", "new", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Does it seem like a weird other world?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "seem", "like", "a", "weird", "other", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Why would he?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "So you're left with a terrible accident.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "left", "with", "a", "terrible", "accident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Have either of you ever heard him speak like that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "either", "of", "you", "ever", "heard", "him", "speak", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What was he planning to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "planning", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "We were going to do short films.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "going", "to", "do", "short", "films", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "How good was Michael Jackson, as an entertainer?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "was", "Michael", "Jackson", ",", "as", "an", "entertainer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "The best.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How good a singer was he?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "a", "singer", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["Amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "And dance-wise, mesmerize?", "question_tokens": ["And", "dance-wise", ",", "mesmerize", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Top.", "answer_tokens": ["Top", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "How do you think, finally, Michael would like to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", ",", "finally", ",", "Michael", "would", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "I think he would like to be remembered as someone that was always, you know, making sure that what he delivered to his fans and to his audience was original.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "would", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "as", "someone", "that", "was", "always", ",", "you", "know", ",", "making", "sure", "that", "what", "he", "delivered", "to", "his", "fans", "and", "to", "his", "audience", "was", "original", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Michael, you were going to say?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", ",", "you", "were", "going", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "I was going to agree with that and say that anything he wanted to do, he wanted it to be the best.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "going", "to", "agree", "with", "that", "and", "say", "that", "anything", "he", "wanted", "to", "do", ",", "he", "wanted", "it", "to", "be", "the", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}]